SUJIN AN

Web/Graphic Designer

+1 647 895 8349 sujin0810@gmail.com

Passionate, creative and confident Graphic Designer with 5 years of full time on-the-job experience ranging from signage, branding to editorial design.

I have been responsible for a webpage, banner, and advertisement designs from concept to final implementation, which allows me to adapt quickly to new and various facets of design material.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

• Feb. 2020 - Oct. 2021

Freelance Designer

- Upon the client's request I produced designs required and suited to their needs from concept to final implementation.
- Produced a variety of logos, editorial, branding and in addition, brochure, business cards and leaflet materials.
- Designed and developed websites using knowledge of HTML, CSS, and JS.

Sep. 2016 – Oct. 2019

Dream S&D Graphic Designer / Hospital Branding and Sign Design

- Responsible for the branding of newly established hospitals and clinics including the logo, exterior signage design, interior signage design, documentation template design business card design, design of hospital marketing material
- Obtained a well-rounded skillset from research, running concept design meeting effective communication skills. project management, site visits, material preparation, site preparation, site/construction supervision and management.
- Worked closely and directly with clients one on one, sharing innovative ideas and bringing them to life.
 Effective communication skills were developed, most importantly listening and understanding the client's needs.

• Feb. 2016 – Aug. 2016

Design Planning & Public Relation Dept Graphic Designer

- Designed material for university events, webpage banners, exhibitions, and marketing in general.
 Worked in collaboration with a team, leading meetings and design scope works hopes and finally implementation.
- May . 2015 Aug . 2015

Design House Editorial Designer

- Worked on editorials and design of a column for the monthly "Designhouse" magazine.

+1 647 895 8349 sujin0810@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Jan . 2022 – Current

Humber College Web Design & Development

- Develop applications with JavaScript, including the latest in open-source frameworks and libraries for front-end applications
- Designing and prototyping interactive interfaces using industry standard tools or applications
- Master the latest specifications for HTML & CSS, including accessible content and design
- Mar. 2014 Feb. 2017

Bucheon University Bachelor's Degree of Industrial Design and UI Design

- Obtained a Bachelor's Degree in Industrial design with a focus in the graphic user interface, brand identity and UI & UX design.
- Scholarship during the course of degree for 3 years.

Awards

- LG Household and Health Care Logo Design Competition Winner
- Best Caligraphy Award
- Coffee Grunaru Package Design Best Design Award

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Adobe Photoshop Adobe Indesign Time management

Adobe Illustration Adobe After Effects Team player

Adobe XD HTML, CSS, JS Deadline-driven

QUALIFICATIONS

- Graphic Technology Qualification Photoshop
- · Graphic Technology Qualification Illustrator

Sujin An +1 647 895 8349 sujin0810@gmail.com 5168 Yonge Street Toronto, ON M2N 0G1

Dear Hiring Manager,

I am writing to apply for the position of Web Designer, which was advertised online at Ontario Public Service Careers.

Over the years, I've gained a Bachelor's Degree in Industrial Design at Bucheon University in Korea. In University, I learned not only overall graphic design skills but also, program tool skills such as Photoshop, Illustrator, and InDesign and also studied UI and UX design. Upon graduating from university, I gained professional experience with 3 years at a signage & graphic design company called "Dream Design", with the recommendation of a professor, and experienced various design projects which are hospital branding design including logo, indoor and outdoor signage, stationery design at the company, growing a lot as a Graphic Designer.

This professional experience has helped me improve my responsibility to lead a design project. From the initial scoping meeting with the client through to design and construction, the experience I gained by leading the project from start to finish helped me obtain leadership, planning, and communication skills.

Having a desire to work in the field as a web designer further, I am currently studying Web Design & Development at Humber College. By the time I graduate from this course I intend to have a high understanding of both graphic and web/app design. I am now able to create a website using HTML, CSS, and JavaScript from my learnings at Humber College.

Highlights of my skills include:

- Website, UX and GUI Design and Web Development: I am able to design a website from scratch.
- Create Interactive Media and Logo design
- Print and Digital Graphic Design: Logo, Stationery, Poster, Advertisement design
- Signage Design: Indoor and outdoor signage design, Banners, Flags

I believe I am a good fit for the role at the Legislative Assembly as I not only have the correct skills to carry out the work, but I also have experience in working with various clients and coworkers from different backgrounds in my previous job.

I would love to find out more about this amazing opportunity at Ontario's Legislative Assembly and let you know how I could benefit your organization.

Thank you for considering my application. I look forward to hearing from you.

Yours sincerely, Sujin An